<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Car Drawing Tutorial</string>
    <!-- Main Menu -->
    <string name="main_title">🚗 Car Drawing 🚗</string>
    <string name="main_title_short">🚗 Car Drawing 🚗</string>
    <string name="main_subtitle">Choose a car you want to draw!</string>
    <string name="language_settings">Language Settings</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <!-- Tutorial Activity -->
    <string name="tutorial_title">Car Drawing Tutorial: %1$s</string>
    <string name="step_indicator">Step %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="tutorial_instructions">Swipe left/right to see the next step</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="select_language">Select Language</string>
    <string name="error_no_tutorial_files">No tutorial files found for this car.</string>
    <string name="error_loading_tutorial">An error occurred while loading the tutorial. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="reward_dialog_title">Reward!</string>
    <string name="reward_dialog_message">Watch an ad to unlock the next step faster, or wait a few seconds.</string>
    <string name="reward_dialog_wait_button">Wait</string>
    <string name="reward_dialog_watch_ad_button">Watch Ad</string>
    <string name="countdown_time_remaining">Time remaining: %1$d seconds</string>
    <string name="countdown_dialog_message">Please wait a moment to unlock the next step, or watch an ad to speed up.</string>
    <string name="countdown_dialog_title">Please Wait</string>
    <!-- Step Descriptions -->
    <string name="car_name_car">Car</string>
    <string name="car_name_car_front_view">Car Front View</string>
    <string name="car_name_firetruck">Firetruck</string>
    <string name="car_name_lamborghini">Lamborghini</string>
    <string name="car_name_monster_truck">Monster Truck</string>
    <string name="car_name_police_car">Police Car</string>
    <string name="car_name_race_car">Race Car</string>
    <string name="car_name_school_bus">School Bus</string>
    <string name="car_name_tractor">Tractor</string>
    <string name="car_name_truck">Truck</string>
    <string name="step_1">Start by drawing the basic shape of the car (rectangle for the car body)</string>
    <string name="step_2">Add two circles below as the wheels</string>
    <string name="step_3">Draw the car roof above the body</string>
    <string name="step_4">Add windows on the roof</string>
    <string name="step_5">Draw the doors and detail lines on the car body</string>
    <string name="step_6">Add the front and rear lights</string>
    <string name="step_7">Add mirrors and door handles</string>
    <string name="step_8">Add details to the wheels (rims, tires)</string>
    <string name="step_9">Add shadows and final details</string>
    <string name="step_10">Color the car as you like</string>
    <string name="step_11">Awesome final car result!</string>
    <string name="step_generic">Step %1$d</string>
    <!-- Car Step Descriptions -->
    <string name="step_1_car">Draw the car roof with a half-oval shape at the top.</string>
    <string name="step_2_car">Draw the curved car body below the roof.</string>
    <string name="step_3_car">Add a curved line at the front of the car.</string>
    <string name="step_4_car">Draw two arches on the lower left side for the wheels.</string>
    <string name="step_5_car">Draw two windows at the top of the car body.</string>
    <string name="step_6_car">Add four circles as the car wheels.</string>
    <string name="step_7_car">Draw small circles inside the wheels as rims.</string>
    <string name="step_8_car">Add door details, body lines, and mirrors to the car.</string>
    <string name="step_9_car">Draw the front bumper of the car.</string>
    <string name="step_10_car">Add two big circles in front as headlights and draw a smiling mouth.</string>
    <string name="step_11_car">Add details to the rear lights.</string>
    <string name="step_12_car">Draw the exhaust at the back of the car.</string>
    <string name="step_13_car">Add details to the door handles.</string>
    <string name="step_14_car">Draw lines on the car hood.</string>
    <string name="step_15_car">Add details to the mirrors.</string>
    <string name="step_16_car">Color the car body.</string>
    <string name="step_17_car">Color the wheels and rims.</string>
    <string name="step_18_car">Color the windows and lights.</string>
    <string name="step_19_car">Add shadows and light effects.</string>
    <string name="step_20_car">Cute cartoon car finished!</string>
    <string name="step_1_car_front_view">Draw the basic front view shape of the car with curved lines at the top and sides.</string>
    <string name="step_2_car_front_view">Add a line for the lower bumper and two small boxes as the wheel bases.</string>
    <string name="step_3_car_front_view">Draw two windshield areas and the hood with two curved lines.</string>
    <string name="step_4_car_front_view">Add four circles on the left and right as headlights.</string>
    <string name="step_5_car_front_view">Draw the grill (air vent) in the center of the front bumper.</string>
    <string name="step_6_car_front_view">Add details to the windshield and hood, such as lines and curves.</string>
    <string name="step_7_car_front_view">Draw two seats, a center mirror, and a steering wheel inside the windshield.</string>
    <string name="step_8_car_front_view">Add side mirrors on the left and right of the car.</string>
    <string name="step_9_car_front_view">Add details to the front grill and a logo in the center.</string>
    <string name="step_10_car_front_view">Color the whole car for a great result!</string>
    <string name="step_1_firetruck">Draw the basic front shape of the firetruck with two big boxes and a rectangle below.</string>
    <string name="step_2_firetruck">Add light details on top of the cabin and the right side of the truck.</string>
    <string name="step_3_firetruck">Draw the front wheel and right side cabin details.</string>
    <string name="step_4_firetruck">Draw the truck body line to the back and add the rear wheel arch.</string>
    <string name="step_5_firetruck">Add windows and doors at the back and the rear wheel.</string>
    <string name="step_6_firetruck">Draw the ladder on top of the truck with two long parallel lines.</string>
    <string name="step_7_firetruck">Add details to the ladder frame on top of the truck.</string>
    <string name="step_8_firetruck">Complete the ladder frame details and lines on the truck body.</string>
    <string name="step_9_firetruck">Add final details like lights, grill, and door handles.</string>
    <string name="step_10_firetruck">Color the whole firetruck to make it look cool!</string>
    <string name="step_1_lamborghini">Draw two big circles as the sports car wheels.</string>
    <string name="step_2_lamborghini">Add rim details to both wheels.</string>
    <string name="step_3_lamborghini">Draw arches above the wheels as front and rear fenders.</string>
    <string name="step_4_lamborghini">Draw the roof and lower body lines, making the car look sleek and low.</string>
    <string name="step_5_lamborghini">Connect the front and rear body lines, then add rim details.</string>
    <string name="step_6_lamborghini">Draw curved lines for the hood and roof.</string>
    <string name="step_7_lamborghini">Add doors, windows, and body line details.</string>
    <string name="step_8_lamborghini">Draw details for the headlights, taillights, and side mirrors.</string>
    <string name="step_9_lamborghini">Emphasize all the lines and shapes of the sports car.</string>
    <string name="step_10_lamborghini">Color the whole car to look like a real Lamborghini!</string>
    <string name="step_1_monster_truck">Draw the basic cabin shape with a box at the top and a long line to the back.</string>
    <string name="step_2_monster_truck">Add side body details with jagged lines for the fenders and rear bed.</string>
    <string name="step_3_monster_truck">Draw the front of the truck and the arches for the front and rear fenders.</string>
    <string name="step_4_monster_truck">Clarify the front shape by adding vertical and horizontal lines.</string>
    <string name="step_5_monster_truck">Thicken the body lines and add details to the cabin for realism.</string>
    <string name="step_6_monster_truck">Draw the front and side windows with curved lines inside the cabin.</string>
    <string name="step_7_monster_truck">Draw two big ovals at the lower left for the rear and front left wheels.</string>
    <string name="step_8_monster_truck">Add two big ovals at the lower right for the front and rear right wheels.</string>
    <string name="step_9_monster_truck">Thicken all four wheels by adding outer lines to each oval.</string>
    <string name="step_10_monster_truck">Draw small circles in the center of each wheel as hubs.</string>
    <string name="step_11_monster_truck">Add hub details to all four wheels with circles and small lines.</string>
    <string name="step_12_monster_truck">Draw jagged patterns on all four tires to make them look like monster truck tires.</string>
    <string name="step_13_monster_truck">Draw mirrors on both sides of the cabin.</string>
    <string name="step_14_monster_truck">Draw two headlights and a grill at the front of the truck.</string>
    <string name="step_15_monster_truck">Add details to the lights and grill with vertical lines.</string>
    <string name="step_16_monster_truck">Draw the rear bed with slanted and horizontal lines.</string>
    <string name="step_17_monster_truck">Add detail lines to the rear bed for clarity.</string>
    <string name="step_18_monster_truck">Draw the front and rear axles connecting the left and right wheels.</string>
    <string name="step_19_monster_truck">Color the headlights yellow and the grill dark.</string>
    <string name="step_20_monster_truck">Color the whole truck green, the wheels gray, and other details as you like.</string>
    <string name="step_1_police_car">Color the background blue as the base.</string>
    <string name="step_2_police_car">Draw the basic car body with curved and straight lines for the roof, hood, and trunk.</string>
    <string name="step_3_police_car">Add curved and vertical lines to define the body and fenders.</string>
    <string name="step_4_police_car">Draw two big windows at the top of the car body.</string>
    <string name="step_5_police_car">Add door details, handles, headlights, and taillights.</string>
    <string name="step_6_police_car">Draw two wheels with rims at the bottom of the car.</string>
    <string name="step_7_police_car">Add mirror, bumper, and lower body line details.</string>
    <string name="step_8_police_car">Draw the siren on the roof and extra details on the front hood.</string>
    <string name="step_9_police_car">Add a star logo and the word POLICE on the car door.</string>
    <string name="step_10_police_car">Color the whole police car as shown, including windows, body, wheels, lights, and siren.</string>
    <string name="step_1_race_car">Color the background blue as the base.</string>
    <string name="step_2_race_car">Draw the basic race car body with curved and sharp lines at the front.</string>
    <string name="step_3_race_car">Add surface details and separation lines on the sides and top of the car.</string>
    <string name="step_4_race_car">Draw the front wing with a box shape at the lower front.</string>
    <string name="step_5_race_car">Add the front wheel with rim and suspension details.</string>
    <string name="step_6_race_car">Draw the rear wheels on the left and right with rim details.</string>
    <string name="step_7_race_car">Draw the rear wing at the top back of the car.</string>
    <string name="step_8_race_car">Add cockpit and driver helmet details in the center of the car.</string>
    <string name="step_9_race_car">Clarify all details, lines, and accents on the race car body.</string>
    <string name="step_10_race_car">Color the whole race car as shown, including the red body, wheels, and driver helmet.</string>
    <string name="step_1_school_bus">Draw a horizontal rectangle at the top as the bus roof.</string>
    <string name="step_2_school_bus">Add vertical and horizontal lines below to form the bus body.</string>
    <string name="step_3_school_bus">Clarify the bus body by closing the right side and thickening the bottom line.</string>
    <string name="step_4_school_bus">Draw two arches below the body for the front and rear wheel spaces.</string>
    <string name="step_5_school_bus">Draw two circles inside the arches as the bus wheels.</string>
    <string name="step_6_school_bus">Add headlights and detail lines at the front of the bus.</string>
    <string name="step_7_school_bus">Draw rectangular windows along the side of the bus.</string>
    <string name="step_8_school_bus">Write "SCHOOL BUS" on the side and add detail lines.</string>
    <string name="step_9_school_bus">Color the whole bus yellow and the windows light blue.</string>
    <string name="step_10_school_bus">Done! Your school bus is complete and ready to go.</string>
    <string name="step_1_tractor">Draw a trapezoid as the base of the tractor cabin at the top.</string>
    <string name="step_2_tractor">Add two rectangles inside the trapezoid for the front and side windows.</string>
    <string name="step_3_tractor">Draw the cabin roof and start a curved line down for the tractor body.</string>
    <string name="step_4_tractor">Continue the body line down and right, forming the front and bottom of the tractor.</string>
    <string name="step_5_tractor">Add a big circle at the back as the rear wheel and a small circle at the front as the front wheel.</string>
    <string name="step_6_tractor">Draw wheel details and add the exhaust on top of the cabin.</string>
    <string name="step_7_tractor">Add grill details at the front and accents on the tractor body.</string>
    <string name="step_8_tractor">Clarify all details, add headlights and wheel accents.</string>
    <string name="step_9_tractor">Color the tractor body yellow and red, and the windows light blue.</string>
    <string name="step_10_tractor">Done! The tractor is ready for the field.</string>
    <string name="step_1_truck">Draw two rectangles, one big (bed) and one small (cabin) on the right.</string>
    <string name="step_2_truck">Add a slanted line from the top of the cabin to the front to form the truck hood.</string>
    <string name="step_3_truck">Connect lines to form the front and bottom of the truck.</string>
    <string name="step_4_truck">Draw arches below the bed and cabin for the front and rear wheel spaces.</string>
    <string name="step_5_truck">Add two big circles as the front and rear wheels.</string>
    <string name="step_6_truck">Draw wheel details and add mirrors and headlights.</string>
    <string name="step_7_truck">Add windows to the cabin and detail lines to the truck bed.</string>
    <string name="step_8_truck">Clarify all details, add door handles and body accents.</string>
    <string name="step_9_truck">Color the truck bed green and the wheels gray and other details.</string>
    <string name="step_10_truck">Done! The truck is ready to carry goods.</string>
    <!-- AdMob Ad Unit IDs -->
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="interstitial_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>
    <string name="rewarded_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/5224354917</string>
</resources>